练习 7-10：对比练习。现在来练习对比。例如，吃骨头的狗
Exercise 7-10, Contrast Practice Now let's work with contrast. For example, the dogs
that eat the bones and the dogs that eat the bones are so close in sound yet so far
apart in meaning that you need to make a special point of recognizing the
difference by listening for content. Repeat each group of sentences, originally
from exercise 7-6, as noted by the numbers in the second column, using sound and
请用声音和语调体现对比。
intonation for contrast. The dogs that eat the bones. The dogs that eat and bones.
The dogs have eating the bones. The dogs have eating the bones. The dogs eats the
bones. The dogs eat the bones. The dogs have eaten the bones. The dogs have eating
the bones. The dogs have eating the bones. The dogs will have eaten the bones. The
dogs will eat the bones. The dogs ought to eat the bones. The dogs can eat the bones.
The dogs can't eat the bones.